loveandlemons.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy - Love and Lemons

Love and Lemons uses Google Analytics and other tracking pixels to collect demographic and advertising information. None of this information is personally identifiable – it is completely anonymous. Love and Lemons may share this information with third parties, primarily for sponsorship purposes.

If you would like to opt-out of providing information to Google Analytics, please use the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Email addresses collected for comments are never used for anything besides comment notification and occasionally for private responses to comments by site administrators. These email addresses will not be sold or distributed to third parties, except for the winners of contests and giveaways, or if a post calls out a specific exclusion to this policy.

Email addresses collected for email subscriptions are are never used for anything besides sending post notification emails. These email addresses will not be sold to third parties or distributed to any third parties except to MailChimp. We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform, and any information transferred to MailChimp will be processed in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) and [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/).

#### Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us [via our contact page](https://www.loveandlemons.com/contact/) ** ** and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

A food blog with fresh, zesty recipes.
